Announcement of this month's salary.
Dedede, Dedede, Dedede.
No, stop it.
Oh, my God, that's disgusting.
Me.
MEME.
MEME YAY! Nice to meet you! What's today's project?
Yay!
You're so hot.
Oh, no.
Today...
I'm at Sendai Station.
I'm...
According to a source...
Tourists are coming to Sendai.
Tourists who come to Sendai
often walk from Sendai Station to Sendai Castle.
To Aoba Castle
They walk there.
That's right.
Have you ever walked there?
No, I haven't.
Of course you haven't.
I've got to go, haven't I? I've got to go, haven't I?
I've got to go, haven't I? Oh, no! I've got to go!
So, today we're going from Chiayo Station to Mount Aosaki!
I'm going to walk!
It's tiring, but we'll do our best!
We'll walk the whole way together!
We'll do our best!
Let's go!
Hello! Let's go! Good afternoon.
Bun, bun, eat one-time.
Bun, bun, eat two-time.
Bun, bun, bun, bun.
Embarrassing.
Hello. - Hello.
Karin, come to the front.
Bye-bye, thank you or bye-bye, thank you, cute
Five thousand yen.
Yay.
Hot.
Summer.
It's summer.
Have any of you been?
Has anyone here ever been on a school trip in the summer? Yes!
School trip.
When I was 11.
It was a bit like a school trip.
Like the speed of sound.
A little bit fast ahead.
But can we stop at something like this?
Aoba's castle.
Where can I go now? To Aoba's Castle? Right now?
Well, then,
Wherever you want to go, right?
Sure, sure.
Where should we go?
Anywhere.
Because I'm close.
Would you like to go for a walk? Usually.
I do.
Do you go for walks? Usually.
I take a walk.
You don't?
Isn't this exhausting?
I'm exhausted.
It's too soon.
We'll take it from here.
You're a spirited girl.
Shouri is a spirited girl, too.
Cheerful kid.
She's hot.
Let's see what happens if we make a sharp turn.
What's it like now? Energy-wise.
I'm fine.
You're fine?
Maybe finally, how are you?
I haven't eaten anything.
I don't have a lot of energy.
But I got a present from Yashwari today.
I got a souvenir from Yashwari.
We all ate it earlier.
Souvenirs from dreamland.
Thank you.
I'm the live-action Mei-chan!
I'm the live-action version of Mei-chan, spreading the wonders of Aoba Castle to the whole world.
I sincerely and strongly want to spread the wonders of Aoba Castle to the whole world.
I see, that's a good dream!
I'd love for you to make it come true and be a radio personality on our radio station.
Why did you come to radio? Well...
Tomorrow...
Every day?
Not tomorrow.
I forgot about that.
You're the MC, right?
Yes, that's right.
May I ask you to say hello too?
Yes, please.
Taran-taran, taran-taran, taran-taran, taran-taran, what day is tomorrow? What day is tomorrow? What day is tomorrow?
What day is tomorrow?
What day tomorrow?
What day is tomorrow? What day is tomorrow? A lot of people lose their sense of reading, so I'll just ask the listeners, then.
Tomorrow is next month.
I think you're going on the radio.
As a listener.
Have you ever been on anything?
Uh...
Dax.
Are you in England?
Can I ask you to say hello?
So that greeting dance you guys do, is that in England? Can I ask him to say hello? Well, I'll do the greeting I always do.
I'm going to do it in England.
Not like you heard it.
Private
Amazing.
Amazing florist, florist and floral shop.
What souvenirs do you recommend?
Souvenirs.
There's one that people don't seem to mention.
I wonder what it is.
Makoron Makoron, a delicious snack, very sweet.
That's great.
There's one more stop.
That's really good.
That's great!
There's a shop!
There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops There are shops
I'll tell you what...
This month...
Salary?
Recording.
I'd like to announce this month's salary... because I'm getting a lot of love.
I'm getting hearts.
I'm getting a lot of hearts.
I get a lot of hearts.
I used to get a lot of hearts, didn't I?
When I was in kindergarten, I used to go to the forest.
I went with my brother to get beetles.
I cried when my brother put a beetle on the sole of my foot.
The soles of your feet?
Doesn't that hurt? When you get on them.
What soles?
You're a maniac.
So, it was a hierarchical thing?
No, I mean, it's not like it's torture or anything.
Well, I said I wanted to try it on.
I said I wanted to put something on, but the soles seemed to have more skin.
So you went for soles.
Gentle, gentle.
That was loud and it hurt.
That's the first time it's ever hurt.
It hurt.
Friend.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's usually something like...
If someone says they're from Sendai or Miyagi...
I already know them.
Yes, you go to the same junior high school, the same high school, the next junior high school, and so on...
Go on.
First is Karen.
I'm...
The rice teacher?
Rice teacher?
Yeah. - Mm-hm.
School lunch lady or school lunch lady, school lunch lady,
I think I'm a school lunch lady!
Fun shop owner
I think she's a fun shop owner!
I think she's doing freeloading too!
I said, I wonder if it's here.
She's definitely not doing it.
They're definitely not doing it.
Definitely not.
I'm definitely not doing it.
I'm not doing it, I'm not doing it, I'm not doing it, I'm not doing it, I'm not doing it, I'm not doing it, I'm not doing it, I'm not doing it, I'm not doing it. No, he's doing it.
I want to do it.
Well, I'll wait.
It's far away.
That's great, it's like a foreigner.
It's true, it's a long way.
But, you know, if you were here as a tourist, you could walk this far, couldn't you?
It's kind of exciting, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm a local.
Is West Park big?
I want to go there.
I want to see the cherry blossoms.
Perfect.
Sendai has wide roads.
Yes, they are.
And the roads are wide.
It's a nice town.
It's nice to live here.
Take a look.
What's this?
It's a green street.
People's Way?
Yes, sir.
What's your name, People girl?
Uh...
West Park Road.
I just said it randomly.
I don't know what you'd call it.
Seriously, you've been going straight for ages.
Yeah, it is.
I can do this on my day off.
It's kind of nice, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
Healthy man.
What's this? The river Hirose?
Hirose River.
Oh, he's already here.
It's the Hirose.
I love nature.
Nature suits you.
What river do you like?
The river?
The Hirose River.
Is this the Hirose?
What river is this?
It's the Hirose River.
I've never seen it before.
It goes all the way up here.
Hello.
I'm Elkameter.
Oh, my God.
What's up, guys?
We're in.
It's so easy to take a picture.
Okay, everybody in?
Everybody in the picture?
We're taking a break.
That's great.
There's some kind of food stall.
I'd like to go there.
Who hasn't eaten since this morning?
No one.
Almost everyone.
I'm off.
We're taking a break.
Fries.
I ordered garlic butter fries.
We all snuggled up together.
They're delicious.
Delicious.
I'm gonna finish my strawberries, but they're so good.
It's amazing.
It's been a long time.
We're here for the festival.
Not a festival.
Okay.
There's an event hall.
Lucky me.
I can't believe this is happening.
After all, they'd be pissed off if we did a gig or something.
It's a sports stage.
I can hear something in your voice.
I want to do it.
That's great.
I'll have some beef tongue from the Shinkansen's predecessor.
Looks delicious!
Bon appétit!
It's not beef tongue.
What?
What do you mean it's not beef tongue? No? No, it's not beef tongue.
Sorry, it's a cow.
Oh, it's a cow.
Do you really feel like a cow?
Countryside.
And do you feel the cow?
And after you eat it, do you say "yeah"?
I mean, do you feel the cow, and after you eat it, do you say "yeah"?
Oh.
Hey, look a bit further ahead.
It's a slope.
It's bad.
It's a bit steep.
I think the customers are starting to push their screens.
Are you all right?
My God! It's huge!
It's huge! That's great!
Rats! Rats!
Worms! Worms!
Oh, my God!
Who couldn't bear worms?
Yes! - What?
What?
Don't get me started on the worms.
Wow! That's disgusting!
That doesn't sound creepy at all.
Mommy.
I'm home.
I'm back!
Oh, is this the owner of the house? I thought you were lost.
Well, then, Rine, I'm lost.
Ma-ma-ma.
The prices at the station are like that, too.
The end.
Isn't this place kind of a leaky spot?
Yes, it is.
The Leaky Cauldron.
Can you please take a picture?
It's a dormant fire.
Great.
There's a komore fire.
Some leak in the sunlight.
And those that leak in the light of a lamp.
It changes your life, doesn't it?
It does.
Momochan, you're a dark person, right?
Momochan, you're a dark person.
Dark people.
I'm a sunshine person.
And you?
You don't want light?
No, I need light.
Aren't you the type that emits your own light?
Yes, I am.
Too much light.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's so easy! You guys try it, isn't it the kind that glows by itself? Yes, yes, it glows all by itself.
Yes, that's right.
It's so easy! Try it, guys.
You've said it before.
It's really easy.
Not really.
Rinu's sweating too.
But Tish is sweating too.
They're hot.
The people filming...
They look cool.
Talking and smiling all the way down.
I'm so tired.
I'm wearing blinkies.
I miss it.
Here we are.
Congratulations on your arrival.
They've arrived.
It's so beautiful.
They rebuilt these stone steps, didn't they?
I see.
Yes, they did.
It's quite beautiful, isn't it?
Wow...
There's a great model.
I can feel the history.
I can feel it.
It's the Tendai.
How did it burn?
If it was on a mountain like this, you'd have a view of everything.
That's for sure.
It's so beautiful.
You can see that too, the Statue of Nara.
The Nara Statue?
Yes, that's right.
It's the distance, isn't it?
Yes, you really do get a bird's eye view.
Heh.
And pasta.
That's amazing.
Yes, it is.
This one's pasta.
Go for this one.
Okay. - Thank you.
Thank you, good luck.
So...
Good job.
Thank you.
That's what I'm talking about.
We've arrived.
Biggest feeling of the day.
It's too much, you can't do it, I'm getting over it now! The greatest feeling of the day! It's too much to climb now, isn't it?
We made it up!
We made it!
Look at the view!
It's beautiful!
It's amazing.
Is it Sendai?
Yes, it is.
How was it? Try climbing it.
Well, I mean, walk up there.
It felt pretty good.
But you saw the sense of nature.
It was amazing.
I've never walked before.
It was fresh.
Maybe I could find a café I want to visit.
Yes, for sure.
You often go to the arcades.
But I just took a few shots of places off the arcade.
I just took a few pictures.
I could see a completely different view.
That's right.
It was like I wasn't in Sendai.
That's true.
I want everyone who lives in Sendai to come.
I want everyone from Sendai to come too.
If you get the chance, please come up here, too.
Yay!
Sendai has many more good things to offer.
There are!
So thank you very much, this generation, there are many more good places to go. Thank you very much. So thank you very much.
Bye-bye!
Let's go home!
Good luck!
YOU